Hello, I'm killin experience
I made that same 5 video [at] one time and now I have decided to ebay it so I started a patreon
What is a patreon said that one guy?
It's a tool to donate a small sum monthly to your favorite creators like a monthly mini Kickstarter
so now you might be saying oh, so the Kilian experience is becoming the next ouya and
What can I say you caught me?
Yeah, [the] plan is eventually to turn my youtube channel into an Android based gaming console, but right now
I want to focus on video Games satire
So if you like the channel and want to pitch in you can do that
And if you hate the channel and also want to pitch in you can also do that
I'm not gonna stop you, but obviously only donate if you have a
Leftover money. I say that before you donate. You should have at least
7 Ferraris you can still donate if you have fewer Ferraris, but make sure you spend money on important stuff first
But killian aren't you getting that Youtube money while yes you get money from ads
But ads don't really care about effort they care about how frequent you post
And how long your videos are that doesn't really work for me because I spent two hours on literally every single
Joke [I]
Need to write a joke about this wizard hMM
What if I say that he's not very good at [being] a wizard okay?
Maybe not every joke but my videos do take a long time to make I wish I could post a new video every day
But I just don't have the improv skills or do
I in [atilla] total who are you but you don't actually play as a [atilla] you can play as other people?
But theater can you even play as a [atilla]? I mean he spawns random at the point 5 [ok] now?
I can't so I spend a lot of time on my videos
I'm spending so much time on the next video that I didn't even prepare my [own] questions for the faq section of this video
I stole someone else's questions, so here we go first question will you be making any more gTA stunts videos?
Yes, does this mean you will charge for videos no I see this in every patreon announcement video has this ever been
Asked if I started to charge for videos ubisoft would send the foreign legion
Will matt make any more appearances pS. Bro Italian I don't
Okay, so I'm starting to see why I should have my own questions
So I'm going to do that
My number one question would be I'm not interested in your patreon at all will dis affect me in any way
the answer is no I
Don't know I was able to do youTube [full-time] from late February to Late March
And I can't make videos faster than that. I can't I have never seen any of your videos
Can you show me something sure but names are important for building a brand?
[I] should probably have shown this set up hMM
If you are interested in more patreon announcement, you should check out another channel, and that is killian experienced